http://www.thedarkking.com/privacy-policy/

Parse error:
syntax error, unexpected T_STRING, expecting T_OLD_FUNCTION or T_FUNCTION or T_VAR or '}' in /home/httpd/vhosts/thedarkking.com/httpdocs/wp-content/plugins/wordpress-support/wordpress-support.php(10) : runtime-created function(1) : eval()'d code(1) : eval()'d code on line 1
TheDarkKing.com - Rate the best Stephen King film adaptation!
Did we miss a Stephen King film adaptation?
Did we miss a Stephen King film adaptation? Just click here and tell us which film you would like to see reviewed on TheDarkKing.com! Or write your own review about a Stephen King film adaptation!
Listed Stephen King Film Adaptations
· The Dead Zone · Dreamcatcher · Hearts in Atlantis · The Green Mile · Dolores Claiborne · Needful things · Misery · Pet Sematary · Christine · The Shining · Carrie
Stephen King Filmography
Complete list of Stephen King movies
Complete list of Stephen King TV films, series and mini series
Complete list of Stephen King short films
Written by Stephen King
Friends and Partners
Stephen King's official website
Celebhoo.com - Find Celebrities
Stephen King - Wikipedia
Stephen King Webring
About TheDarkKing.com
Home
Contact us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Resources
Copyright
Copyright ©2020 by TheDarkKing.com. All rights reserved.
Contact us for reprint permission.
Links welcome.
Privacy Policy
TheDarkKing.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.
Our site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use visitor contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The visitor’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
This site contains links to other sites. TheDarkKing.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
We may run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The visitor’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We also use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Public Forums
TheDarkKing.com makes forums, message boards, polls and surveys available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
TheDarkKing.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control such as routine backups and administrator-only server access.
Children’s Guidelines
TheDarkKing.com meets the guidelines of TRUSTe’s Children’s program and therefore:
Does NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child’s request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.
Does NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent.
Does NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information without prior parental consent.
Does NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.
Does NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.
Choice/Opt-Out
TheDarkKing.com provides visitors the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives visitors the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
Use our contact form
Correct/Update
TheDarkKing.com gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
Use our contact form
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of TheDarkKing.com, or your dealings with this web site, please make use of our contact form.
© 2020 TheDarkKing.com - A website which honors the dark side of Stephen King.
Disclaimer: All trademarks and copyrights owned by their respective owners.
